Good morning,
ladies and gentlemen of the twelve bishops.
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
This is a holy day where we celebrate
the advent of our God...
Pope Guitane
Let us ensure the festival is a success.
Yes, as unfortunate as the rain might be.
That's likely my fault.
The rain tends to follow
me around, I'm afraid.
And I'm afraid your welcome parade
will have to be canceled.
Beyond that, the rest will
be as you were informed...
You will each inspect different
areas of the church,
with members of our team
serving as your guards.
Wait, why are we being separated
from His Holiness?!
Archbishop Ganmo
It's part of Prince Albert's
plan to defend us.
Apparently, the man who attacked the
Daen Cathedral may be something of a misotheist.
I imagine he's counting on it being easier
to keep us safe when we are not all together.
Yes, sir.
Well, it's not like we
can tell them the truth.
That it's really to keep an eye out for
the monster hidden among them.
Rest assured, we will do everything
possible to keep you safe.
Archbishop Anastasia
We'll now escort you to your
appointed areas for inspection,
so if you'd please enter your coaches.
Your Holiness, if you'll come this way.
Bishop Anastasia, I will be escorting you.
I'll be in your care.
I don't like this.
I don't need a guard. If anyone
was stupid enough to attack me...
Archbishop Batts
I'd kick their ass before sending
them straight to the Lord.
Batts, men shouldn't run
their mouths so much.
Archbishop Dante
It's all about communicating with your back.
What're you talking about, Dante?
Backs don't even have mouths.
This is why you're an idiot.
Who are you calling an idiot, asshole?!
E-Excuse me...
Archbishop Yataro
Right this way, Bishop Dante.
I dare you to say it again!
Dante! We're not done, you hear me?!
Archbishop Melissa
We're headed this way.
Hands off, you old bag!
I'm talking to Dante over here!
Damn it, how are you so strong?!
Thank you for your protection.
Not exactly friendly, is he?
Who am I supposed to be guarding?
Gimme a hottie! I want a hottie!
I think it's them.
Archbishop Akamaki
No, there's still a chance!
I'm supposed to be guarding one other person!
This time it'll be a hottie!
Looks like that's them.
Archbishop Aomaki
Right this way...
What's with the doleful demeanor?!
Get it together!
It's you, isn't it?
The one who said that the Daen Cathedral was
attacked by someone dressed like a pastor.
Archbishop Rozelis
Right.
And you seem to think that this person is
actually a member of the Church, it seems.
You wretch!
Archbishop Thor
How dare you insult us like that?!
What are you plotting?!
Now, Thor, calm down.
So, do you have any leads on the attacker?
Well... no.
I would imagine it'd be easier to
guard us if we were all together.
Right this way, my good bishops!
Wait just a minute!
What's that in your hand there?
Just a drink to set the tone
for this important duty.
Archbishop Chloe
Would you care for some, Your Grace?
Fool! And you're supposed to protect us?!
So sorry about that, sir!
Episode 19: The Great Advent Festival
Father.
The Pope will be arriving soon.
It's been so long since I've seen Guitane.
You've known each other
for a long time, right?
Oh yes, long before I was king
and Guitane became pope.
If one of the bishops is
the mysterious pastor...
Splitting them up like this should remove
any chance of assassinating the pope.
Here's hoping there're
no unexpected twists...
His Holiness's coach has arrived.
It's good to see you again, Your Holiness.
I hope you can forgive any
offenses I may have caused.
Oh, Albert!
You've grown so much.
Guitane!
Charles!
When I heard you'd be personally
inspecting the church,
I made sure our schedules would line up!
I'm sure you're just here for
your daughter's recital.
It's true, I do love Saria.
Despite her getting my name
wrong, occasionally...
Chan!
Chan!!
It's Charles, your daddy, dear!
It's Charles, your daddy, dear♥
Oh? Shouldn't you be angry
about that sort of thing?
There's actually something I'm looking
forward to even more, today.
What's that?
Gentlemen, perhaps you should
discuss this inside?
I can't help being anxious.
Considering how light security is...
Actually, do you not
sing anymore yourself?
There's a prohibition on weapons
inside of the Advent Festival.
Oh, come now... that's ancient history.
You would think that'd make
things more safe, but...
I guess being Pope leaves you
with little time for music.
Given that the enemy can shapeshift,
this likeness might not be of much use.
But does anything come to mind?
No.
Well, more like it's inconceivable.
I understand the situation, but it's too
late to cancel the Advent Festival.
You'll have to proceed with the
investigation after it's over...
You can arrange security to your liking
on the day of, in the meantime.
If anything happens...
I might not compare to
you, Your Majesty...
I'm counting on you.
But I'm not who I used to be, either.
Here's hoping nothing happens...
Let the event play out,
let the people enjoy themselves.
And then everyone comes back safely.
Has there always been a cutie
like her at this church?
Wait, that's a sister?!
Well, she arrived with
Bishop Anastasia, didn't she?
Really...?
You seem to be getting
more attention than I am.
Would you consider joining the
cloth instead of being a maid?
Archbishop Anastasia.
If you are the mysterious pastor,
or are working with him...
that would be the worst-case scenario.
A different outfit?
Yes, if you're going to be guarding me
all day, then you should look the part.
Understood. If you would loan me a habit...
I know it's for my protection, but you
really shouldn't have this kind of thing.
Let's find a habit with a
shorter skirt, for you.
She's as sharp as I'd heard.
And she works directly for the pope...
The closest woman to him.
I'll just have to pray...
That she isn't an enemy.
Good grief. Even without a sword,
she gives off this intensity.
Rumble
The other bishops were in groups of two
per their guards, but I'm here alone...
And with the Silver Blader, no less.
This will make getting anything
done extremely difficult.
I'm also a bit curious about the crows that
haven't flown from the roof, despite the rain.
But... it shouldn't pose any real problem.
You all should have imagined multiple
levels beyond the worst-case scenario.
Looks like it's starting.
Not the kind of performance
I'd expect from a church!
What are those? Bass drums?
What was that?! What happened?!
Guards!
What?! What happened?
Everyone, remain calm...
Something's going on outside...
It's the gates of hell.
That was the sound of them
breaking open, Charles.
I was hoping you'd have a priority
seat to watch this show.
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
Forgive me for the imposition
during such a trying time.
But we consider you a candidate
to be the next pope...
Will you undergo the
ritual to become pope...
Guitane?
This involves bathing
you with our Luma Maxima.
If you are able to withstand it while
maintaining purity of heart...
then you are, without a doubt,
a saint... and worthy of being pope.
Luma Maxima.
There are no shadows in my soul.
Nothing to repent for.
Magnificent! He is truly remarkable!
Not even the slightest reaction!
Imagine, not having even the slightest
speck of wickedness in your soul!
Especially after what happened!
They were wrong.
In that moment,
something was confirmed for me.
That the black, coiling sensation
I felt taking root within me
was far more wicked than how
the gods defined evil.
And that no ray of light
could ever reach it.
My faith in that abyss runs
as deeply as its depths.
Things seem to be quite
noisy outside, Charles.
I had originally planned for chimeras to
emerge from beneath this church, too, but...
Albert already dismantled that facility.
It won't pose a problem, though.
My forces will wash over
this country like a wave...
What's with the hole?
It opened up out of nowhere.
Until it is submerged...
and annihilated.
Run! Monsters!
Unbelievable!
The person we were protecting is
the one we should've gone after!
It's Father we should have been protecting!
You'll be next, Albert.
Considering you are the heir
to King Charles's will...
Though to be honest, I intend on eliminating
everyone who abides by God's will.
This nation's laws were constructed
on a basis of divine teachings.
"Do not kill. Do not deceive. Do not steal."
All these things that everyone
takes for granted...
And all of it's wrong.
Killing, stealing...
None of it matters, you see.
If the will behind them is pure...
Guitane!
That voice...
I believe this is our first time meeting,
Angel Jihriel.
And after everything I've
done, your boss...
God, still refuses to descend
to earth, it seems.
I was hoping my rampage might have
been enough to compel God's intervention.
What did this to you?!
Depending on your answer, I may
have to cast judgment on you myself!
Is that one of the sacred envoys
that bestows divine sorcery?
What is this?!
His Holiness?!
Perhaps I can restrain him
with that kind of help?
There's one enemy... and Father is there...
Can we manage this without
harming Father or the guests?
I don't owe you any answers.
No...
What is that?!
The King!
Is that a monster?! But it's the Pope!
Someone get some soldiers!
When I saw that likeness...
it reminded me of how you
looked when you were young.
Or rather...
It brought to mind what your boy would
have looked like... had he lived.
Is that what happened... to change you so?
Charles.
Are you satisfied with
those as your last words?
Father!
Your Majesty!
Sir Angel... never mind me... save Albert!
And let my two children know...
that I'm sorry I couldn't
witness their recital!
Angel! Don't worry about me!
My Father! Protect my Father!
No need to worry.
The entire royal family will be
sent to the heavens...
And you'll be able to listen
to the performance from there.
Your children's sweet music.
Save my father!
Wait... His... two children?
Having taken my leave from
Paradise without permission...
This is who I serve... in the mortal realm.
Thinking back, it was that moment
where we passed by each other.
That boy who appeared behind me so suddenly.
The chill he gave me...
What I had overlooked...
Could I have even imagined such
a wonderful miscalculation?
As a human, I could not
reach the heavens.
So I would raise my banner of rebellion
by snuffing out a nation...
And the faith in the god that it follows.
Or perhaps, destroying the country
would give God cause to descend
in an attempt to judge me.
I'd been clinging to that
faint hope for so long.
I'm so grateful. With your death,
my descent into the abyss will be complete.
Someone who could make me feel this way...
Descending upon me, with
an angel in his service...
If you are not a god, then what are you?
I'm just a prince.
The seventh one, at that.
Boom
What the—?!
Father?! Al?! Where'd you come from?!
Dian?! Is this Saloum Castle?
What in the world...?
I should be asking that!
Does this have anything to do with
the commotion in the streets?
That's right, Dian! I need your help!
Father...
The enemy can change his form at will.
That's why I'm sure he was just
disguising himself as His Holiness!
No...
You're right.
It must be an impostor.
Notify all soldiers in the castle!
Our enemy has occupied the Daen Cathedral!
Defend our citizens at all costs!
Seeing him in person made it clear.
Clear how little I understand, rather.
Mana condensation and manipulation
of his mana apertures...
To conceal his presence, he is
expending a massive amount of mana
with each passing second, pointlessly.
You've a knack for hiding your
presence... much like I do.
Prince Lloyd! Escher and
Princess Saria are safe!
All right.
I want the two of you to help the
people fighting in the city.
There are way more chimeras running
amok than I anticipated.
And I'm going to have my
hands full with this guy.
Please, wait! This is personal for me!
Please, allow me to—
You can't beat him.
Is that how tough he is?
It just occurred to me,
couldn't you teleport to the mysterious
pastor by detecting his mana?
Not with how short our
little encounter was...
Plus, his mana gave off the
faintest presence at the time.
Looking back, he probably does the
same thing I do... conceals it.
He's definitely suppressing his mana.
He might be on par with a demon...
maybe even a Demon Lord!
I'm gonna have to pass.
You're gonna do some crazy crap
like fight without a barrier
to sample his attacks
if I leave, aren't you?
Will not!
You promise?!
I do!
You better not, then!
Come on, Jihriel!
Unholy Excalibur.
You're not going anywhere, Jihri—
Mana focus: Impulsa Incinis.
Divine Septuple.
Guitane.
There's a whole lot that I'd
like to discuss with you.
But before that... there's something I've
been wanting to tell you in person.
You've crossed a line.
I'm a rainy fellow.
And it feels like no matter how much it rains,
it can never quench what I feel in my heart...
Next time, Episode 20:
"Invasion."
Episode 20
m 0 0 l 436 0 l 456 24 l 436 48 l 20 48 l 0 24 l 20 0
Invasion
You will witness the depths of sorcery.